propwall.my 2016-06-27

# Privacy | Propwall

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Propwall collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.propwall.my website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Propwall. 

## Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

## Non-Personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

## Web Browser Cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

## How We Use Collected Information

Propwall may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:   \- To personalize user experience, we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users use the services and resources provided on our Site. \- To generate marketing leads, we may use information to match the appropriate advertisers on our Site. \- To send periodic emails, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

## How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

## Sharing Your Personal Information

We may share aggregated Users personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

Propwall has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

## Your Acceptance Of These Terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

## Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA)

By agreeing to the terms and conditions contained herein, you hereby allow The Star media group to collect your Personal Information to be regulated and managed by The Star media group. You also hereby agree to receive the latest information about products, news and events updates, rewards and promotions, special privileges and initiatives from The Star media group, its partners and advertisers. Click [here](http://clips.thestar.com.my/docs/Privacy_Policy.pdf) to view the full Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to receive the above, kindly call 03- 7967 1388, ext: 1861 or email to [support@propwall.com](mailto:support@propwall.com).

This document was last updated on March 31, 2016
